Guide to the Lillian Herlands Hornstein Papers 1930-1980 MC.140
New York University Archives
- Series I.c: Chaucer's Manuscripts
  - Index card collection, related to Chaucer's MLT, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04058130 1
  - Caxton Advertisement. Framed., undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - WASP Siege Prioress, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Japanese publication, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Chaucers Canterbury Pilgrims Print, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Caxton and the Early Printers. A collection of contemporary documents and Prints compiled by Sylvie Nichels, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Series II: NYU Class-Related Material
  The section on Margaret Schlauch includes articles, notes, personal travel notebooks, correspondence, postcards and class silyabi. The published articles are ordered by year. The rest of the section is ordered mainly by class title and number or by field (like Linguistics, Medieval English Lit, and Humanities). (Boxes 10/7-13/1.c, see also 18/30)
  - Schlauch, Margaret. NYU professor of 'Hornstein's and later colleague that moved to teach in Poland, they shared a lot of common academic interests. Articles, notes, personal travel notebooks, correspondence, postcards and portrait (?) and class syllabi., undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04058131 9
  - Schlauch, Margaret. Publications and articles (1920s and 1930s), 19201939 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Schlauch, Margaret. Publications and articles (1940s), 19401949 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Schlauch, Margaret. Publications and articles (1950s on), 19501959 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Schlauch, romance notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 15th Century Literary English class, Hoccleve, Lydgale, Beryn James, King Gawain, Douglas, Caxton-Troy and colloquial english, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 15th Century, texts, chronology, subjects for reports, outlines, exams, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Malory, papers, articles, manuscript, publications, mainly about the death of Arthur, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - About the Round Table, publication of images on King Arthur's myth fromt he Metrolpolitan Museum of Art, New York, 1945., undated (Box 11, Folder 8.b)
  - Linguistics I. International Phonetc also Alphabet, notes, bibliographies, and clipping about a universal non-language. "We try harder" multilingual pins. Origins of language. Morphemes. Stylistics, Oxymoron theory., undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Linguistics II. German 252, Principles of linguistic science, 1961. Linguistics, Spring 1970., 19611970 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Linguistics class exams, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Medieval English Literature I, English 211-212, syllabus and materials 1958-1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04058132 7
  - Medieval English Literature II, ibid., undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Medieval English Literature III, ibid., undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - English 33.2 Greek, Latin and Medieval Literature, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - English 33-34. Medieval Lit in translation (also Slauch's Eng. 47-48), undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - English 213-214. Medieval Lit. from the Norman Conquest through Malory, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Medieval Literature Bibliographies I, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Medieval Literature Bibliographies II, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Medieval Romance and Satire, outlines and Reading Lists, undated (Box 12, Folder 8.b)
  - Outlines for medieval lit. and bibliographies, undated (Box 12, Folder 8.c)
  - Dissertations to be read, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Comprehensive PhD exams, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Cambridge University Examination Papers, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Problems in the Origins and Development of the English Language, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Apothemgs, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Old English verbs, pronouns and nouns, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Humanism, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Humanities 5-6. Outlines, exams, notes, papers on Plato, Vergil, Plutarch, Dante, Chaucer, the book of Job for class., undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Huntington Library, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Development of Modern English. Exams., undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - History of Language. Materials for class 201-202. Grimm and Verner's Law, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04058128 5
  - History of Language. Materials for class 201-202. Grimm and Verner's Law cont., undated (Box 13, Folder 1.b)
  - English 201-202. Exams., undated (Box 13, Folder 1.c)
- Series III: Linguistics
  Folders kept in original order, it's not alphabetical. It includes clippings, articles,notes, publications. See also Box 11/9-11 for NYU class material on Linguistics. (Boxes13/1.d-14/26)
  - 17, 18, 19th Century English Language, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Animal Language. Nature of language, definition of LInguistics, Phonetic, Phonemis., undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Comparitive study of language-Different approaches, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Definitions. Analogy, affricative, alliterations, assimilation, etc. Also, Excresecent, enclitic, etimology, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Alphabet. Runes, Writing scripts, written systems, theory. Jotham Johnson, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - British versus American English, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Compound words/Conversion Separable, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Check LIsts, Growth of vocabulary, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Dialects. Dissimilation, Diphtong, derivation, euphuestic style, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - English/American dialects. Substandards, Slang, American-Indian dialects. Modern Brit. Cumberland Dialect. Scottish Dialect., undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Dictionary, making of, misc. pamphlets and notes of existing dictionaries., undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Etymology. (see also folder 10, box 11 for popular etymology), undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Germanic language, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Grammar, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Indoeuropean Language. Families/Method., undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Old English. Gospels, Matthew 6:9-13 Lords Prayer. Luke 15:11-24 Prodigal Son. Luke 10:30-35 Translated. Proclamation of woman. Anglo-Saxon Chronicle. Alfred's Law code, the ten commandments. Caedman's hymn. Laws of Aedelberht, King of Kent, 560-616., undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Old English II. Celtic, Danish, Latin influence. English/Gothic/Sdskr/Latin/Greek. Verb in Old and Middle English. Vulgar Latin Inscriptions. Dialects. The English Tripos, Part I and II, May, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - International Language, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04058133 5
  - Linguistic terms starting with J,L,M, and N., undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Linguistic terms starting with O,Q,R, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Linguistic terms starting with S,U,V,Z, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Law and Language, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Changes of Meaning, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Ogham, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Palindrome and Phonetics, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Phonemes and Spelling, Phonology, Phonetic Alphabet., undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Popular etimology, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Preface, to a linguistics dictionar. Paradigm, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Sounds of English, Phonemics and Punctuation, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Poetic language, undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Rosetta Stone, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Semantics, language, and society, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Syntax, Spelling, Standard, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Structural Linguistics, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Transformational Grammar, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Vowel Positions, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Early English Text Society. Correspondence, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Names of food and people, undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - World languages, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Law-French Dictionary, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Linguistic Atlas of New England, undated (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Britain, British Council. Includes issues of Britain/USA '87, MLA Newsletter. Volume 21, Number 1. Pamphlets and correspondence with the British council., undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Middle English, undated (Box 14, Folder 26.a)
  - Gorlach. Anglistiches Seminar. Correspondence, Middle English texts publication from University of Heidelberg of which Ms. Hornstein was on the advisory board., undated (Box 14, Folder 26.b)
  - Languages of the World. Includes English as a international language. International Auxiliary Language Association, Interlingua, undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Series IV: Miscellaneous Research Material
  Also, personal interest articles, notes, correspondence. This section is in a ratherchaotic order. Check for extra or missing material in the other sections. There are fileson Authographs, Iconography, the Female Serpent, Israel, Folklore and Folktales, Medievaldrama and Music, 15c Arthurian Saga, Zodiac, Bocaccio, Freud, Jung, Jack Kerouac andDieting. There are also prints and posters in the last two boxes. (Boxes 14/27-25)
  - Dedications, undated (Box 14, Folder 27.b)
  - Modern Authors: Cynthia Ozick, John Updike, Tom Wolfe, Sidney Hook., undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Academy of literary studies, meetings, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Muscatine, Charles. "Poetry and Crisis in the Age of Chaucer" 900-1190, undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Newstead, Hellen. Publications and Papers, correspondence, undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Utley, Francis Lee, undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Greek Tragedy, undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Hugo Schmerber. Die Schlange Des Paradieses, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04058134 3
  - American Journal of Archaeology, Vol. XXI, No. 3., undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Iconography of the Chapter House, Salisbury Cathedral. Includes Photographs., undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Church ornaments. Includes Scriptorum, int. review of manuscript studies. The Funeral of Renart the Fox from the Book of Hours, by Florence McCulloch, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Female serpent Collection. Several images and articles., undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Female serpent I, Hornstein work, notes, bibliographies,etc., undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Female serpent II, undated (Box 15, Folder 6.b)
  - Female serpent III, undated (Box 15, Folder 6.c)
  - Dr. W.O.Hassall correspondence. Bodleian Library, Oxford. Related to, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Female serpent collection's correspondence., undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Illuminated Manuscripts from Chicago Collections correspondence and catalog, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Austen, Jane. Article about estate, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Pogo catoon on Garden of Eden, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - The York Tercentenary Lectures Approaches to Paradise Lost., undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Bibliographies on Iconography, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified manuscript, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Sir Amadace and the Avowing of Arthur Two Romances from the Ireland MS. by Christopher Brookhouse. Anglistica, Copenhagen., undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Harvey. The Playbill. Theatre program, letter and clippings, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Russell, Bertrand. Words and Thoughts Index card collection of bibliographies, from A to Z., undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Barclay, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04058135 0
  - Bible, Mount Sinai manuscript, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Chaucer class, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Colkelbie Sow, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Coghill, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Norman. Merton College, Oxford. Correspondence., undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Declaration of Independence, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Edel, Leon. Correspondence, clippings, and article: "Psychoanalysis and the "Creative Arts", undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - English contemporary criticism. Articles, notes, clippings, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Epic, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Folktales and Folklore. Prof. Greet, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Hamilton, Marie, correspondence and articles, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Hawes, Stephen. Bibliography, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Early Humanists, undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Lindsay, David, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Legal learning of Chaucer's Serjeant-of-the-Law, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Loomis, Roger and Laura, correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Lord Berners, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Love, Nicholas, undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Literature of Instruction. The Seven Sins, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Mackellar, Walter. Correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Medieval Epic, bibliographies, assignments, Negro in the Middle Ages, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Medieval Music, 14th century, undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Medieval Drama, undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Medieval Romance and Satire, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Medieval Dialects. McIntosh, Angus. A new approach to middle english, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Mersand, Joseph. Articles about teaching Engish in High Schools., undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Miller, Edwin. Holiday cards., undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Phillips Moe, recommendation letter., undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Music, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Nancy Dean. Vita, articles., undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - NEH Fellowship application of Susan Schulz, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Charles of Orleans, undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - William of Palerme, undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Peacock, Reginald, undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Early Printers, undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Raymo, Robert A. Correspondence, undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Reich. Wedding invitation and memorabilia, undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Russell, Earl. clippings (to copy), undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Severs, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Seven Sages, undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Saracens, undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Shirley, undated (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Syr Triamour, including early printed editions, undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Sqyr of Lowe Degree, undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Swords, double-edged and chastity, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Scottish Literary History. Figures, Characteristics and Bibliography., undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Thomas of Erceldoune, bibliography, undated (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Titus and Vespasian. Siege of Jerusalem, undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Torrent, undated (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Zodiac, related to Chaucer, undated (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Brunne's poem Handlyng Synne. Proposal and Manuscript for a Hornstein edition to the 15th Century Bowes-Midland manuscript of Robert Mannyng from the Osborn collection at Yale University, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04058136 8
  - Handlyng Synne, A Modern English Translation with Textual Notes, by James, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Epistle to Othea, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Thomas More among the lawyers. Edited by Daniel G. Collins, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Concerning Pigmalion by Hope Weissman, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Critical Approaches to Six Major English Works: Beowulf through Paradise Lost, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - The Middle English miracles of the Virgin, by Beverly Boyd, 1964. How the, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - The Book of Margery Kempe, by Colonel V. Butler-Bowdon, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - An Alphabet of Tales, an English 15th Century translation of the Alphabetum, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - 15th Century Bibliographies and notes., undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Steven Arts, Deadly Sins, Virtues and Wonders, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Arthurian Celtic. Articles by Loomis, Helaine Newstead and, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Loomis-Arthurian Romance, undated (Box 17, Folder 12.b)
  - Arthurian Symbolism, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Arthur after the 15th Century., undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Arthurian Artifacts, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - International Arthurian, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Mallory-Allit Morte Arthur. Relation to Alexander, stanzaic and chronicles, undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Irish Arthurian Romances, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - English Arthurian and Gowain Poems, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Arthurian Terms Papers, Drama, 3 Morte's, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - 15th. Century Course Notes, Outline of assignments, Readings Lists, Subjects, undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - 15C Transition, Literary, Satire. Libel of English Policy and Political, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - 15C Social Criticism: Mum, PPCreed, London Sickpenny, Ploughliman's Tale, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - 15C Chaucer Apocryphea, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Romans of Partenay or of Lusignan, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Capystranus, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Romances of Charlemagne, undated (Box 17, Folder 26.b)
  - Chevalry, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Clariodus, Sir Cleges, Damusta Saga, Degarc, Degrevant, undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Eleanor of Acquitaine, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Eger and Grime, undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Eglamour Home, undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Geoffrey of Monmouth, undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Tristan, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Troilus and Criseyde, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Trobadours. Romance Courtly love. Meaning of Cortaysye, undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - English Alliterative Romances, undated (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Alexander Legend, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Amadace, undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Amis and Amiloun, Apollonious, undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Development, biblio, themes, Authorship. Romanticism 18-19 C., undated (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Myth, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04058137 6
  - Queries. Bodleian library, Lincoln Cathedral, PML, Huntington, College of Arms Lambeth Palace, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - St. Eustace, Fiercebras, Floriant et Forete, Floris and Blanchefleur, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Gamelyn, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Siege, the destruction of Jerusalem, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cotton Nero. Julius Caesar. Percy, Thomas., undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Le bone Florence. Dissertation proposal by Carol Falvo Heffernan., undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Sir Gawain and the Green Knight, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Sir Gawain and the Green Knight cont., undated (Box 18, Folder 8.b)
  - Henryson, undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Dunbar, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Beowulf, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Beves of Hampton, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Anglo Saxon, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Academy of Literary Studies, correspondence, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Bible, articles and materials about Judeo-Christian religions, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Richard Holland Owl and Peacock, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - James I of Scotland, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Athleston and Sir Gowther, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - American History, Historian Morrison's obituary., undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - American Places Names, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - ***Autographs, including Fred Astaire's and Isaac Bashevis Singer, undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Anthony and Cleopatra, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Allegory, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Federaion, undated (Box 18, Folder 23.b)
  - Animals, apes and boars and Animadversions, undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Best Sellers, undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Brass Rubbing, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - British Habits, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Joyce Cary, undated (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Celtic, undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Classics, problems, undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Comparative Literature, GSAS, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Icelandic Literature, undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Inns of Court, undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Hebrew, undated (Box 18, Folder 33.b)
  - Israel, undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Jewish, undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Japan, undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Joyce, James Bibliography, Portrait, Finnegan's Wake, Ulysses, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04058138 4
  - Henry James on American Speech, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Faulkner, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Latin, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Law, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lectures, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - La Fonaine, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Lovers, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Lamb, Charles, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Luther, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Lyric, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Magic, medieval, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Mababharta, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - May Day, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Medieval Academy Club, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Melville, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Milton, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - MHRA, Modern Humanities Research, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Monastic Manuscript Microfilm Project, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Museum of Natural History, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Naturalism. Dissertation about the American War Novel, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Hyder Edward Rollins, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Novel. Assignments, Reading lists from other Professors, and thesis proposal, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Norwegian Literature, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - O'Casey, Sean., undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Oxford, undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Paleography, undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Pastoral, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Petrarch, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - PhD Questions, written and oral. Student records., undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Plato, undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Plagiarism, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - PMLA, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Proverbs, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Quotable, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Speculum, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Rabelais, undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Realism-Naturalism, undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Renaissance, reformation, undated (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Romanticism, undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Rethoric, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Rome, undated (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Ruskin, John, undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Satire, undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Saga and Russia, undated (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Scandinavian Literature, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04058139 2
  - Sturm und Drang and Nibelungen, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Science, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Shakespeare, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Shakespeare Sonnets, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Southey and Coleridge, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Stonehenge, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Strindberg, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Swift, Jonathan, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Swinburne, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Synge, John Millington, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Teaching, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Tennyson, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Tests, undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Theocritus, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Utopia, undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Voltaire, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Warsaw. Article by A.M. Rosenthal in the New York Times Magazine, undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Whitman, Walt, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - MLA correspondence, articles and research in progress, MLA newsletter, undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Thomas Usk, biographical notes, Study on Testament of Love, undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Eli Silvestein Meat and Poultry Market calendar with religious stories on them, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Translation., undated (Box 20, Folder 23)